Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
8094
Afrika Bambaataa, 1957-
600 cubic feet.
Vinyl records and other A/V Recordings, Financial Records, Manuscripts, Memorabilia, Photocopies, Photographs, Printed Materials, Publications.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Approximately 40,000 sound recordings representing Bambaataa's music collection from the 1970s to the present. The archive also includes books, documents, and files relating to the founding and spread of the Universal Zulu Nation; and videos, papers, and clothing.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Afrika Bambaataa is an American disc jockey, singer, and songwriter from the South Bronx, New York. Often called the “Godfather” of Hip Hop, Bambaataa has helped to define Hip Hop since it emerged in the South Bronx in the 1970s. One of a handful of Hip Hop's 1970s originators, Bambaataa gave Hip Hop its name, and was the first to define its core artistic elements - DJing, rapping, break dancing, and graffiti art - under one cultural umbrella. His cultural organization, the Universal Zulu Nation, has helped to spread Hip Hop culture throughout the world. His genre-defining 1982 song "Planet Rock" and subsequent electro-funk tracks have become icons of hip-hop and electronic music. In 2007 he was nominated for induction into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Approximately 40,000 sound recordings representing Bambaataa's music collection from the 1970s to the present. The archive also includes books, documents, and files relating to the founding and spread of the Universal Zulu Nation; and videos, papers, and clothing.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Afrika Bambaataa, 1957-; Universal Zulu Nation (Organization)
Subjects:
African American youth -- Social life and customs.; Disc jockeys.; Electronic music.; Funk (Music).; Hip-hop.; Hip-hop -- Influence.; Hip-hop -- History. -- United States; Music -- Social aspects.; Race relations.; Rap (Music); Rap (Music) -- Political aspects.; Rap musicians.; Hip-hop -- New York.; Rap (Music) -- New York.; Hip-hop; Rap (Music); Rap musicians; Social history
Places:
Bronx (New York, N.Y.) -- Social conditions -- 20th century.; New York (State) -- New York; New York (State) -- Bronx; United States
Form and Genre Terms:
History
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Access to collection restricted until completion of processing, with the exception of vinyl records that have been individually cataloged.
SERIES LIST
Series I. Manuscripts
a. School Papers and Assignments
b. Africa Trip
c. Soul Scrapbooks and Music Writing
d. Notebooks and Miscellaneous Manuscripts
e. Lyrics and Poems
f. Bronx River Neighborhood Center
g. Phone and Contact Lists
Series II. Flyers
Series III. Photographs
Series IV. Personal Papers
a. Personal Papers
b. Press About Bambaataa
c. Catalogs and Mail
Series V. Universal Zulu Nation Documents
a. Infinity Lessons
b. Administration
Series VI. Stage Costumes and Clothing
Series VII. Periodicals and Publications
a. Small Press Publications
b. Periodicals
c. Publications from 3410 De Reimer Ave. Bronx, NY
d. Other Publications
Series VIII. Moving images and audio recordings
a. Video cassettes
a. Audio cassettes
Series IX. Music collection
12 inch vinyl
Sureshots and altered/obscured
Numbered by Bambaataa
Annotated, not numbered (Alphabetical by artist)
A-D
E-H
I-L
L-O
P-S
T-Z
Numbers, unknown and various
Second alpha sequence
Cataloged individually
Not annotated (Alphabetical by artist)
A
B
C
D
E
F
G
H
I
J
K
L
M
N
O
P
Q
R
S
Afrika Bambaataa recordings
Renegades of Rhythm Tour
Test pressings and white labels (not yet cataloged)
Compilations (not yet cataloged)
7 inch vinyl
Numbered (not yet cataloged)
Annotated not numbered (not yet cataloged)
No annotations (not yet cataloged)
Acetates and lacquer discs
Cassettes (not yet cataloged)
CDs (not yet cataloged)
Series X. Ephemera
CONTAINER LIST
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Not annotated
      Series contains vinyl discs that are either not annotated or the annotations are small and were missed during the sorting of discs. While some effort was taken to bring together piences that were dense in copy-specific track preferences. These items are arranged in alphabetical order by artists’ last name or the name of the group. Each letter of the alphabet has a subseries. Compilations, soundtracks, and other albums with various artists are in subseries together. Artists and groups whose names start with a number are in a separate subseries. Most artists are alphabetized under the name they are most well-known as (e.g. Puff Daddy; Prince; Fela). The variations of names are contained in the Creator field. In a few cases, however, artists’ aliases were unknown, and they may have been listed under two different artist names.
      - A
        - A-ha - The sun always shines on T.V., 1985; SR-10393; A-ha (Box 166)
          In same jacket as # SR-10394. 2 copies
          Catalog # 0-20410; A-side Matrix # 0-20410-A-SH-1 B-22222-SH1
          Warner Bros. Records Inc.
          Burbank, California
        - A-ha - The sun always shines on T.V., 1985; SR-10394; A-ha (Box 166)
          In same jacket as # SR-10393. 2 copies
        - A-Ko - Chicago, 2005; SR-10395; A-Ko (Box 166)
          In same jacket as # SR-10396. 2 copies
          Catalog # MPM022; A-side Matrix # BB44656-01-A1 MK
          Melting Pot Music
          Cologne, Germany
        - A-Ko - Chicago, 2005; SR-10396; A-Ko (Box 166)
          In same jacket as # SR-10395. 2 copies
        - A Sides - Once again; Stick up kid, 1999; SR-10397; A Sides (Box 166)
          Catalog # East 24; A-side Matrix # EAST-024-AA
          East Side Records
          Essex, United Kingdom
        - A-Town Players - True players, 1995; SR-10398; A-Town Players; Black Coffy; Mixzo (Box 166)
          Catalog # PRO-A-7906; A-side Matrix # 0-43631/PRO-A-7906-A-SR1-SP
          Premeditated
        - A-Town Players - True players, 1995; SR-10399; A-Town Players; Black Coffy; Mixzo (Box 166)
          In same jacket as # SR-10400. 2 copies
        - A-Town Players - True players, 1995; SR-10400; A-Town Players; Black Coffy; Mixzo (Box 166)
          In same jacket as # SR-10399. 2 copies
        - A-Town Players - Player can't you see, 1998; SR-10401; A-Town Players; Envyi; Mixzo (Box 166)
          Catalog # ED-6075; A-side Matrix # ST-ED-6075A-1
          EastWest Records
          New York, New York
        - A-Town Players - Wassup, wassup!, 1995; SR-10402; A-Town Players (Box 166)
          Catalog # PRO-A-7678; A-side Matrix # PRO-A-7678-A SR1
        - A+ - It's on you; Watcha weigh me, 1999; SR-10403; A+; Debarge, Chico; Massenburg, Kedar (Box 166)
          In same jacket as # SR-10404. 2 copies
          Catalog # U8P-1455; A-side Matrix # U8P-1455 A
          Kedar Entertainment
          Motown
        - A+ - It's on you; Watcha weigh me, 1999; SR-10404; A+; Debarge, Chico; Massenburg, Kedar (Box 166)
          In same jacket as # SR-10403. 2 copies
        - A+ - Enjoy yourself, 1998; SR-10405; A+; Fyffe, Ty; Massenburg, Kedar (Box 166)
          Catalog # U8P-1378; A-side Matrix # U8P-1378 A
          Universal Records
        - A3 - Ain't goin' to Goa, 1997; SR-10406; A3; Ministers at Work; Simply Jeff (Box 166)
          Catalog # PRO-A-1129; A-side Matrix # PRO-A-1129-GEF-A-GL1
          Geffen Records
          Los Angeles, California
        - Aaliyah - One in a million, 1996; SR-10407; Aaliyah; Mosley, Tim; Elliott, Missy (Box 166)
          Catalog # PR-6936; A-side Matrix # ST-PR-84283-1
          Blackground Enterprises
        - Abbott, Gregory - I got the feeling, 1986; SR-10408; Abbott, Gregory (Box 166)
          Catalog # 44-06710; A-side Matrix # XSS175823-1B
          Columbia Records
        - Abbott, Gregory - Shake you down, 1986; SR-10409; Abbott, Gregory (Box 166)
          Catalog # C 40437; A-side Matrix # AL40437-1F
        - ABC - How to be a zillionaire, 1985; SR-10410; ABC (Box 166)
          Catalog # PRO 397-1; A-side Matrix # PRO 3971-AS
          Mercury
        - ABC - The look of love, 1982; SR-10411; ABC (Box 166)
          In same jacket as # SR-10412. 2 copies
          Catalog # MDS 4023; A-side Matrix # MDS-4023-2-56988-PRC-C-2-1
        - ABC - The look of love, 1982; SR-10412; ABC (Box 166)
          In same jacket as # SR-10411. 2 copies
        - ABC - Vanity kills, 1985; SR-10413; ABC (Box 166)
          Catalog # 884 714-1; A-side Matrix # 884-714-1-2-5849912-ES
        - ABC - Poison arrow, 1983; SR-10414; ABC (Box 166)
          In same jacket as # SR-10415. 2 copies
          Catalog # 811 329-1; A-side Matrix # 811 329-1 AS E4-1-1 PRC-C
        - ABC - Poison arrow, 1983; SR-10415; ABC (Box 166)
          In same jacket as # SR-10414. 2 copies
        - ABC - The night you murdered love, 1987; SR-10416; ABC (Box 166)
          Catalog # 888 894-1; A-side Matrix # 888-894-1-AS-SP
        - ABC - The night you murdered love, 1985; SR-10417; ABC (Box 166)
          Catalog # 884 714-1; A-side Matrix # 884-714-1-2-58499-12-ES
        - ABC - When Smokey sings, 1987; SR-10418; ABC (Box 166)
          Catalog # 888 726-1; A-side Matrix # 888726-1-AS-ES
        - ABC - That was then but this is now, 1983; SR-10419; ABC (Box 166)
          Catalog # NTX 105; A-side Matrix # NTX 105 A // 1 420 H
          Neutron
          Sheffield, United Kingdom
        - ABC - The look of love, 1982; SR-10420; ABC (Box 166)
          Catalog # NTX 103; A-side Matrix # NTX 103 A // 1 420 H
        - Abdul, Paula - My love is for real (Disc One), 1995; SR-10421; Abdul, Paula (Box 166)
          In same jacket as # SR-10422. Double album
          Catalog # SPRO-38497; A-side Matrix # PAULA 2-12-A FUTURE DISC
          Virgin Records America, Inc.
        - Abdul, Paula - My love is for real (Disc Two), 1995; SR-10422; Abdul, Paula (Box 166)
          In same jacket as # SR-10421. Double album
        - Abdula - Fantasias; Love so right, 1995; SR-10423; Abdula (Box 166)
          Catalog # 115903161-A; A-side Matrix # 115.903.161.A
          Continental
          Sao Paolo, Brazil
        - Abdula - Joguei com seu coração; You give love a bad name, 1995; SR-10424; Abdula (Box 166)
          Catalog # 115903162-A; A-side Matrix # 115.903.162.A
        - Abdula - É bom te amar; Não posso te perder, 1995; SR-10425; Abdula (Box 166)
          Catalog # 115903160-A; A-side Matrix # 115.903.160.A
        - Abdula - Vem me ver; Depende de nós, 1995; SR-10426; Abdula (Box 166)
          Catalog # 115903159-A; A-side Matrix # 115.903.159.A
        - Abdula - Sublime deusa funk; Spring love, 1995; SR-10427; Abdula (Box 166)
          Catalog # 115903163-A; A-side Matrix # 115.903.163.A
        - A.B.L. - High IQ; If you want it, 2000; SR-10428; A.B.L.; DSS (Box 166)
          Catalog # 60355 72031; A-side Matrix # DR 7203-A
          Dech'm Records
          U.S.A.
        - Abnormal Yellow Band - Funky oreo 2000, 2001; SR-10429; Abnormal Yellow Band (Box 166)
          In same jacket as # SR-10430. 2 copies. Annotated
          Catalog # unknown; A-side Matrix # DLP-004-A
          Delic Records
          Tokyo, Japan
        - Abnormal Yellow Band - Funky oreo 2000, 2001; SR-10430; Abnormal Yellow Band (Box 166)
          In same jacket as # SR-10429. 2 copies. Annotated
        - Above The Law - Black Superman, 1994; SR-10431; Above The Law (Box 166)
          Catalog # RPROLP-0290; A-side Matrix # RPROLP-0290-A
          Ruthless Records
        - Above The Law - Livin' like hustlers, 1990; SR-10432; Above The Law (Box 166)
          Catalog # E 46041; A-side Matrix # PAL-46041-1A
        - Above The Law - Call it what u want, 1992; SR-10433; Above The Law (Box 166)
          Catalog # 0-40837; A-side Matrix # 0-40837-A-SR-1
        - Above The Law - Time will reveal, 1996; SR-10434; Above The Law (Box 166)
          Catalog # TB 1154 A; A-side Matrix # TB-1154-A2
          Tommy Boy Music
        - Above The Law - Untouchable, 1990; SR-10435; Above The Law (Box 166)
          Catalog # EAS 2121; A-side Matrix # XSS-02121A-1A
        - Above The Law - Murder rap; Another execution, 1990; SR-10436; Above The Law (Box 166)
          In same jacket as # SR-10437. 2 copies. Annotated
          Catalog # 49 73155; A-side Matrix # XSS-73155A-1A G1
        - Above The Law - Murder rap; Another execution, 1990; SR-10437; Above The Law (Box 166)
          In same jacket as # SR-10436. 2 copies. Annotated
        - Above The Law - Kalifornia, 1995; SR-10438; Above The Law (Box 166)
          Catalog # 88561-6324-1; A-side Matrix # 88561-6324-1 A
        - Absolute - Heat, 1998; SR-10442; Absolute (Box 166)
          Catalog # Def 264-1; A-side Matrix # DEF-264-1-A
          Def Jam Recordings
        - Abstrac' - Right and hype, 1989; SR-10443; Abstrac' (Box 166)
          Catalog # PRO-A-3620; A-side Matrix # PROA23620-SR1
          Reprise Records
        - Abyale - I wanna be…Remixed, 1991; SR-10444; Abyale (Box 166)
          Catalog # 656407 8; A-side Matrix # 14-COL 656407 (8A)-21-5A1A
          France
        - A.C. Groovers - You say wot, 1990; SR-10445; A.C. Groovers (Box 166)
          Catalog # BB 2004 MX; A-side Matrix # BB 2004 MX A
          Bull & Butcher Recordings
          Italy
        - Accomplice - 遠い道のり (Distino Longe), 2002; SR-10446; Accomplice (Box 166)
          Catalog # FLRS-014; A-side Matrix # FLRS-014 A
          Flower Records
        - Accorsi, Martin - Immersed; Feedback inhibition (Disc One), 2001; SR-10447; Accorsi, Martin (Box 167)
          In same jacket as # SR-10448. Double album
          Catalog # YR066; A-side Matrix # YR-066 A2
          Yoshitoshi Recordings
          Washington, D.C.
        - Accorsi, Martin - Immersed; Feedback inhibition (Disc Two), 2001; SR-10448; Accorsi, Martin (Box 167)
          In same jacket as # SR-10447. Double album
          Catalog # YR066; A-side Matrix # YR-066 C2
        - Ace Of Clubs - Tribal knight, 1990; SR-10449; Ace Of Clubs (Box 167)
          Catalog # TLKDJ1; A-side Matrix # TLKDJ 1 A-1J-1-1
          Talkin' Loud
          United Kingdom
        - Aceyalone - All balls don't bounce (Disc One), 1995; SR-10450; Aceyalone (Box 167)
          In same jacket as # SR-10451. Double album
          Catalog # C1 7243 8 30023 1-3; A-side Matrix # C1-1-30023-G1
          Capitol Records
          Hollywood, California
        - Aceyalone - All balls don't bounce (Disc Two), 1995; SR-10451; Aceyalone (Box 167)
          In same jacket as # SR-10450. Double album
          Catalog # C1 7243 8 30023 1-3; A-side Matrix # C1-3-30023-G1
        - Acoj - Except me, 1986; SR-10452; Acoj (Box 167)
          In same jacket as # SR-10453. 2 copies
          Catalog # 4Z9-05947; A-side Matrix # 4Z 905 947-4-1C
          CBS Associated Records
        - Acoj - Except me, 1986; SR-10453; Acoj (Box 167)
          In same jacket as # SR-10452. 2 copies
        - Adam And The Ants - Antmusic EP, 1982; SR-10454; Adam And The Ants (Box 167)
          Catalog # DUNIT 20; A-side Matrix # DUN-IT-20-A1
          Do It Records
          London, United Kingdom
        - Adams, Bryan - Let me take you dancing, 1979; SR-10455; Adams, Bryan (Box 167)
          Catalog # SP-12014; A-side Matrix # SP 12028
          A&M Disco
          United States
        - Adams, Felicia - Thinking about you, 1994; SR-10456; Adams, Felicia (Box 167)
          Catalog # 374631208-1; A-side Matrix # 37463 1208-1A
          Motown Record Company
        - Adams, G. - Chicken scratch, 1983; SR-10713; Adams, G. (Box 167)
          Catalog # MG 110; A-side Matrix # MG-110-A
          Moonglow Records
        - ADC Band - Renaissance, 1980; SR-10457; ADC Band (Box 167)
          Catalog # SD 5221; A-side Matrix # ST-CTN-804473-A
          Cotillion Records
        - ADC Band - Roll with the punches, 1982; SR-10458; ADC Band (Box 167)
          Catalog # DMD 312; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-40827-1
        - Cannonball Adderly Quintet - Hummin'; Summer song, 1996; SR-10459; Cannonball Adderly Quintet; Foster, Ronnie; Large Professor (Box 167)
          Catalog # SPRO 7087 6 10118 1 4; A-side Matrix # SPRO-10118
          Blue Note
        - Cannonball Adderly Quintet - Hummin'; Summer song, 1996; SR-10714; Cannonball Adderly Quintet; Foster, Ronnie; Large Professor (Box 167)
        - Adderly, Tony - I ain't mad at you, 1983; SR-10460; Adderly, Tony (Box 167)
          Catalog # CW 80912; A-side Matrix # CW-80912-A
          Clockwork Records
        - Addis Black Widow - Innocent, 1995; SR-10461; Addis Black Widow (Box 167)
          Catalog # 12BB2; A-side Matrix # 12BB2A
          Breakin Bread
          Stockholm, Sweden
        - Addy, Mustapha Tettey - Master drummer from Ghana volume 2, 1980; SR-10462; Addy, Mustapha Tettey (Box 167)
          Catalog # TGS 139; A-side Matrix # TGS 139 A
          Tangent Records
        - Addy, Mustapha Tettey - Solo drumming, 1984; SR-10463; Addy, Mustapha Tettey (Box 167)
          Catalog # T 884 002; A-side Matrix # 668832F-A1+C
          Insel Hombroich
          Germany
        - King Sunny Ade & His African Beats - Bobby, 1983; SR-10464; King Sunny Ade & His African Beats; Ade, Sunny (Box 167)
          Catalog # ADE 71; A-side Matrix # ADE 71 FIS
          Sunny Alade
          Nigeria
        - King Sunny Ade & His African Beats - Ma Jaiye Oni, 1982; SR-10599; King Sunny Ade & His African Beats; Ade, Sunny (Box 167)
          Catalog # IPR 2054; A-side Matrix # IPR 2054 A-2U-1-1
          Island Records
        - King Sunny Ade & His African Beats - Aura, 1984; SR-10600; King Sunny Ade & His African Beats; Ade, Sunny (Box 167)
          Catalog # 90177-1; A-side Matrix # ST-IL845499-A
        - Adebambo, Jean - Reaching for a goal, 1981; SR-10465; Adebambo, Jean (Box 167)
          Annotated
          Catalog # TWDIS 46; A-side Matrix # TWDIS 46A
          Third World
        - Adeva - Warning!, 1989; SR-10466; Adeva (Box 167)
          In same jacket as # SR-10467. 2 copies
          Catalog # V-15544; A-side Matrix # V-1-15544-Z2
        - Adeva - Warning!, 1989; SR-10467; Adeva (Box 167)
          In same jacket as # SR-10466. 2 copies
        - Adichie - Full time baby, 1992; SR-10468; Adichie (Box 167)
          Catalog # WAR-117; A-side Matrix # WAR-117-A
          Warlock Records
        - Adioa - Toubab bi lé, 1987; SR-10469; Adioa (Box 167)
          Catalog # AO 1064; A-side Matrix # ADIOA 1064 A
          Drouin Records
        - A.D.O.R. - One for the trouble, 1994; SR-10470; A.D.O.R. (Box 167)
          Catalog # 0-85641; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-72225-72828-7289-1
          Atlantic
        - Adrenaline - Damn that DJ made my day, 2001; SR-10471; Adrenaline (Box 167)
          Catalog # TB2243; A-side Matrix # TB-2243-A
          Tommy Boy Silver Label
        - Adrenaline - Shut the f*** up + dance, 2000; SR-10472; Adrenaline (Box 167)
          Catalog # TBV2082b; A-side Matrix # TBV 2082B A1
        - Advanced Chemistry - Fremd im eigenen land, 1992; SR-10473; Advanced Chemistry (Box 167)
          Catalog # AC 01 V12"92; A-side Matrix # AC 01 V12 92 A1
          Mzee Records
        - Aeon FX - Research, 1997; SR-10474; Aeon FX (Box 167)
          Catalog # DOS049; A-side Matrix # DOS 049-A1
          Dos Or Die Recordings
        - Aeschylus - The church of you, 2000; SR-10475; Aeschylus (Box 167)
          Catalog # INS6018-12; A-side Matrix # INS 6018-1 A
          Insiduous Records
        - Affinity - Don't go away, 1983; SR-10476; Affinity (Box 167)
          Catalog # PRO 7808; A-side Matrix # PRO-7808-A
          Mango
        - Affinity - Pick me up, 1986; SR-10477; Affinity (Box 167)
          Catalog # PRO 417; A-side Matrix # PRO-417-A
          Pow Wow Records
        - Various Artists - Africa- ancient ceremonies dance music and songs of Ghana, 1979; SR-10478; Various Artists (Box 167)
          Catalog # H-72082; A-side Matrix # H-72082-A-SP
          Nonesuch Records
        - Africali - Ayiko bia, 1983; SR-10479; Africali (Box 167)
          Catalog # DESZ-7504; A-side Matrix # DEZS-7504-A Z2
          East Street Records
        - A.B.U. Nation - Pat em down, 1996; SR-10480; A.B.U. Nation (Box 167)
          Catalog # WP002; A-side Matrix # WP-002-A
          Solidify Records
        - African Business - In Zaire business, 1990; SR-10481; African Business (Box 167)
          Catalog # URBX 64; A-side Matrix # URBX 64 A-1J-1-1
          Urban
        - African Connection - Tiembelema, 1984; SR-10482; African Connection (Box 167)
          In same jacket as # SR-10483. 2 copies
          Catalog # CEL 177; A-side Matrix # CEL-177-A-RE
          Celluloid
        - African Connection - Tiembelema, 1984; SR-10483; African Connection (Box 167)
          In same jacket as # SR-10482. 2 copies
        - African Image - Roots; Izimpande, 1984; SR-10484; African Image (Box 167)
          Catalog # GR 8306; A-side Matrix # GR-8306-A1
          Gramavision Studios
        - African Music Machine - Black water gold, 1972; SR-10485; African Music Machine (Box 167)
          Catalog # LPS 3317; A-side Matrix # LPS-3317A
          Soul Power Records
          Shreveport, Louisiana
        - Africanism - Bisou sucré, 2000; SR-10486; Africanism (Box 167)
          Catalog # YP085; A-side Matrix # YP 085
          Yellow Productions
          Paris, France
        - Afro Super-Feelings - I like women, 2001; SR-10487; Afro Super-Feelings (Box 167)
          Catalog # SPLP 002; A-side Matrix # SPLP002 A
          Soul Patrol Records
        - Afro Cuban Band - Bang bang, 2000; SR-10488; Afro Cuban Band; Matos, Noey (Box 167)
          Catalog # JEL2574-A; A-side Matrix # JEL2574-SA
          Jellybean Recordings
        - Afro Kid - Shooks; The rolla, 1996; SR-10715; Afro Kid (Box 167)
          In same jacket as # SR-10716. 2 copies
          Catalog # CR009; A-side Matrix # CR009A1
          Chronic
        - Afro Kid - Shooks; The rolla, 1996; SR-10716; Afro Kid (Box 167)
          In same jacket as # SR-10715. 2 copies
        - Afro-Plane - Shine, 1994; SR-10489; Afro-Plane (Box 167)
          Catalog # RDAB 62915-1; A-side Matrix # RDAB-62915-1-A
          Kaper Records
        - Afro-Plane - Afro-plane (Disc One), 1994; SR-10490; Afro-Plane (Box 167)
          In same jacket as # SR-10491. Double album
          Catalog # RDAB 66291-1; A-side Matrix # RDAB 66291 1 A
        - Afro-Plane - Afro-plane (Disc Two), 1994; SR-10491; Afro-Plane (Box 167)
          In same jacket as # SR-10490. Double album
        - Afro-Rican - This is how it should be done, 1990; SR-10492; Afro-Rican (Box 167)
          Catalog # GR-139; A-side Matrix # GR-139-A
          Luke Skywalker Records
          Liberty City, Florida
        - Afrodisiac Sound System - Afroheat #1, 2004; SR-10493; Afrodisiac Sound System (Box 167)
          Catalog # AFROHEAT1; A-side Matrix # ASS 001-A
          Afrodisiac Records
        - Afroman - Crazy rap, 2001; SR-10494; Afroman (Box 167)
          Catalog # UNIR 20657-1; A-side Matrix # UNIR-20657-1A
        - Afros - Kickin' afrolistics, 1990; SR-10495; Afros (Box 167)
          In same jacket as # SR-10496. 2 copies
          Catalog # 44 73590; A-side Matrix # XSS-73590-A-1A
        - Afros - Kickin' afrolistics, 1990; SR-10496; Afros (Box 167)
          In same jacket as # SR-10495. 2 copies
        - After The Fire - Der kommissar, 1982; SR-10497; After The Fire (Box 167)
          In same jacket as # SR-10498. 2 copies
          Catalog # XSS 170754; A-side Matrix # XSS170754
          Epic Records
        - After The Fire - Der kommissar, 1982; SR-10498; After The Fire (Box 167)
          In same jacket as # SR-10497. 2 copies